So what is Thai tea?
It is very popular of course in Thailand but now it is gaining quite a big following in the US.
It is served in all different types of tea houses as well as in Thai restaurants.
It is made up of black tea usually from China.
It is ancaramum (phonetic) and anise and cinnamon but also orange food coloring.
That is what gives it an orange color.
When you are drinking Thai tea keep in mind it is caffeinated because it has black tea leaves in it.
And Thai tea is usually consumed when it is sweet so also if you are afraid of sugar and calories stay away from Thai tea.
But it is a wonderful treat to try if you want to enter into the Asian cuisines and touch upon what is popular in different Asian tea houses.
Because Thai tea is the best selling tea in a lot of places that sell boba and various sweet stuff in different tea houses throughout the United States.